scurri.co.uk 2014-04-09

# Privacy Policy | Scurri

### IMPORTANT – PLEASE READ CAREFULLY

Scurri Webservices Ltd (the “Company”) knows that privacy is important to you, our customer and we want you to know that we are looking out for you. Information about how we gather and share data collected through this application is noted below. 

We at Scurri Webservices Ltd ensure your privacy is protected at all times. Our privacy policy will explain how we use the information you provide us with, and how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy. For the purpose of this policy, the terms “you” and “your” shall mean Members. By visiting this website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

* * *

### The information we collect and how we use it

\- When you register for our service we need to know your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number. We may also need to know other information from time to time which we will request when necessary. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for the purpose of making your on-site experience easier. 

\- Scurri Webservices Ltd gathers this information to allow us to process your registration, process any Transactions you may enter into and process any payments to be made as a result of entering into such Transactions. The relevant information is then used by us, our agents and sub-contractors to provide you with statements of your account (or as required) and to communicate with you on any matter relating to the conduct of your account and the provision of the Services in general. 

\- We may also use aggregate information (so no individual Members are identified) and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the website and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual. 

\- From time to time we may provide your information to a customer service agency for research and analysis purposes so that we can monitor and improve the Services we provide. We or our agents and sub-contractors may contact you by post, e-mail or telephone to ask you for your feedback and comments on our Services. 

\- We may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please send an email message containing “No further information” in the Subject box, to info@scurri.co.uk 

\- If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, phone calls or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

\- We may also want to provide you with related information from third parties we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please send an e-mail to info@scurri.co.uk We may also provide your information to carefully selected third parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not wish us to disclose your information in this way, please send an e-mail to info@scurri.co.uk 

* * *

### Cookies

A “cookie” is a small software file stored temporarily or placed on your computer’s hard drive. The main purpose of a cookie is to allow a web server to identify your computer and web browser, and tailor web pages and/or login information to your preferences. Cookies help us promptly display the information you need to use the capabilities of the Scurri.co.uk website and other information which we consider to be of interest to you. 

The list below describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari etc.)

We utilize various categories of cookies, which are summarized below along with the options available to you to manage them.

**Essential:** Essential cookies are those that are critical to the functionality of the Scurri.co.uk website. We use these cookies to keep a user logged into Scurri and remember relevant information when the user returns to the Service.

**Non-Essential:** We use non-essential cookies to track users’ activities while using Scurri.co.uk, understand their preferences and improve their user experience.

Please note that if you do elect to disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies, you may not be able to access or take advantage of many features on our website.  
These are cookies that are set by this website.

**First Party Cookies**

**Google Analytics:** We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information.We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.

**Third Party Cookies**  
These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site that allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook and Google+. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website. You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information. 

* * *

### How we protect your information

The internet is not a secure medium. However we have put in place various security procedures as set out in this policy and Domain SSL Cerificate   
We also keep your information confidential. Our internal procedures cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information. Furthermore we will comply in all respects with the provisions of the Data Protection Act 1998. 

* * *

### Sale of business

If any of the information that you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, name or payment details or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to info@scurri.co.uk

* * *

### Your consent

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times.

* * *

### How to contact Scurri Webservices Ltd

Scurri Webservices Ltd welcomes the views of its members about our website and our privacy policy. If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments please send an e-mail to info@scurri.co.uk 

Private Company Limited by Shares. Registered in Ireland 483417. Strand Road, Duncannon, New Ross, Co. Wexford, Ireland.  
‪Directors: R. O’Connor, J. O’Connor, E. Crehan, P. Nolan, B. Patterson, B. O’Keeffe, G. Riordan.
